They voted for Donald Trump.
Yeah.
You know, it's a lot of people.
So you can't just pigeonhole them and say you just don't care and you're racist or whatever you're thinking.
This is an act of I don't know what else to do.
I just wish we had more leaders that were figuring out how to do more for the middle class, for the working folk.
Is the middle class in the room with us?
Who's the middle class?
At this point, like genuinely, who is the middle class?
Because can't nobody afford a house.
Can't nobody afford tuition.
Everybody got loans out the ass.
So who is the actual middle class?
Those are the folks who are drowning in this economy.
It's not me anymore, but I know those folks and they're good people and they don't have a way out.
And that makes for bad choices.
So according to Michelle Obama, people voted for Donald Trump because they were desperate, because they were broke, not because they're racist, not because they're sexist, not because they're idiots, not because they are selfish, not because they're narcissists.
It's just because they didn't know what to do.
Now, I know y'all swear by this lady, but let me just decode what she's saying for you.
What she's literally saying is, you know, those people that voted for Trump are not bad people.
You know, all the people that y'all are talking about every time you say, you know, they voted for this.
You know, all the people that you're talking about every time you're like, this is why a black woman will never win.
She's saying, you know, we can't forget those voters.
Now, mind you, she's not saying we can't forget the voters who were against the genocide and work with them.
That's not what she's saying.
She's saying we need to make it our business to really try and get the voters who voted for Trump to come over to our side because we care about them.
Flat twist.
No one cares about any of you.
And until you really understand that, nothing will happen.
We need to be putting our energy into creating systems outside of the system.
And let me tell you, you're not starting from scratch.
People have been doing this for quite some time, and it's time for us all to put our energy into that and take our energy away from folks like Michelle Obama,
who was giving Werther's originals to a war criminal, just like her husband, a.k.a. Bush.
Y'all really be believing these people, and I don't understand why.
They will call me all type of names, but listen to this nonsense.
If we are not disengaging to build something better, we are simply continuing to hold up the thing that's holding us down.